Evans, W. Duane, Additional Papers /3091
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
W. Duane Evans Additional Papers
1952-1969
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Evans, W. Duane
/3091
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
Papers mostly on the subject of statistics.
3082420
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3029: W. Duane Evans Papers
Evans, W. Duane.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Faculty.
3082420
- U.S. Department of Labor Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1947-1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- Evans Cigarette Report Vol. 2, 1916-1934 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Evans Cigarette Report Vo. 2, 1923-1935 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Explanatory Bulletins of The Interindustry Relations Study for 1947 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Chemicals Reports of the Interindustry Relations Study for 1947 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Industrial Productivity, 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Productivity - Cohn Paper, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- War Labor Administration World War 1, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- [Original Folder Titled: "Am. Un. - 2nd Sem. 1951-2"], 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Domar, Evsey, Theoretical Analyses of Economic Growth, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Agr. Grad. Sch. - 1st Sem., 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Am. Univ. - 49-50 1st Sem Survey Records, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Stat. Exams, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Agr. Grad. Sch. 1st Sem. 40-41, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- U.S. Department of Labor, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Interindustry Relations Study for 1947 Unpublished Material Book 3 of 4 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Interindustry Relations Study for 1947 Unpublished Material Book 1 of 4 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- AACP - BLS Reports, 1947-1953 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Statistics - Miscellaneous Material to book on Sampling, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Statistics - Course Outlines, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Lectures, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Stat. - Papers Int. Stat. Conf., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Statistics - Method of Adjusting BLS Indexes, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Productivity - International - Power Use Differences - Olson, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Statistics Abstract, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Seasonal Adjust. Confidence Factor Approach (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Prof. W.D. Evans, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Envelope
- Outliers, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Simulation Weighting Samples of 5, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Notes and Abstracts, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Sum of Powers of Integers (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Wage Formula, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Estimation of Input Coefficients (Box 2, Folder 16)
- U.S. Department of Labor - Full Employment Patterns, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Derivation of Capital Coefficients for Machine Tools, Metalworking Machinery, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- IO Projects - Prospective, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Cochran, William G., 1950 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Statistics - Reprints (Box 2, Folder 21)
- W. Duane Evans, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Statistics - Reprints, 1948-1957 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Cornell - Misc., 1964 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Misc. (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Iteration - Dynamic (Box 2, Folder 26)
- 'Productivity of Living Standards, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Satisfaction (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Ry (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Statistics - Interpolation, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 30)